Let me out of here! Please!
放我出去 拜托你们
Silence, Elephas!
闭嘴 艾雷法斯
Many women and children are being held hostage in the royal capital.
还有许多女性和孩童 在皇都被当人质
Are you all going to sacrifice them?
你们打算牺牲他们吗
How dare you say that after you begged the empress dowager and betrayed your tribe?
背叛族人 向皇太后摇尾求怜的家伙 还好意思说这些
We will control the Demon King on your behalf and attack the capital.
我们会代替你操纵魔王 然后进攻皇都
What plans do you have for the future?
之后 你有什么打算
Miss Aileen.
爱琳小姐
So, this incident was caused because a coup d'etat was planned.
原来这次的事件 是为了政变
If it's not stopped immediately, the Levi clan will be wiped out.
若不尽快阻止 雷比一族真的会被灭族
In the end, it is just as Lilia said, the future will not change.
到最后 还是如莉莉安小姐所说 未来无法改变
Miss Lilia?
莉莉安小姐
You're indeed with Lilia...
你果然跟莉莉安同谋…
No. To be specific, I work for Empress Dowager.
不 正确说来 是替皇太后办事
It's just that I'm...
只是我…
with Lilia one-sided...
单方面对莉莉安小姐…
What's wrong? Why are you looking at me like dirt?
怎么了 为什么把我当脏东西看待
Nothing. Please go on.
没什么 继续说
About half a year ago, I had my first conversation with Miss Lilia.
大约半年前 我初次与莉莉安小姐对话
Forget it.
还是算了
She must have told you
她八成对你说
"You worked so hard but it doesn't seem to be working out. What a pity."
"看你这么辛苦却无法得到回报" "好可怜哦"
Your heart skipped a beat then.
然后你就小鹿乱撞了吧
How innocent.
太单纯了吧
Could you please not ruin my beautiful memories.
可否请你…不要毁了我的美好回忆
Then, she must have told you the Levi's would head towards an end, right?
然后 她跟你说 雷比一族会走向末路 对吧
That's right.
没错
I see.
原来如此
She had also gotten back the power of the Scared Sword.
而且 她取回了圣剑的力量
I borrowed the Sacred Sword from her...
我跟她借了圣剑…
All of those were my work.
这一切…都是我做的…
She had me there.
被她摆了一道
I did not expect her to take down Elephas first
没想到她居然先攻略艾雷法斯
and took actions that are the complete opposites of the game.
并采取与游戏完全相反的行动
I have no more magic now to escape from prison.
现在我已无魔力 无法从牢里出来
Why don't you have magic?
为什么没魔力了
You took my magic away with the Sacred Sword.
你用圣剑把我的魔力夺走了
I happen to land in my homeland.
好死不死 坠落的地点 正好在我的故乡
Is that so? The Sacred Sword took away your magic?
是哦 圣剑夺走了你的魔力…
No wonder I'm feeling energetic.
难怪我还这么有精神
It seems like I have the ability to save your people.
看来 我似乎有能力拯救你的族人
Do you have anything you want to say?
有没有什么想说的
But I...
可是我…
Stop pretending in front of me.
别跟我装可怜
I will never forgive you for what you did to Almond.
杏仁的事情 我绝不原谅你
Beg me for mercy.
厚着脸皮求我
Kneel and ask for my forgiveness.
跪下来请求我的原谅
This way... I can...
这样…我就可以…
face Almond...
面对杏仁了…
What are you doing?
你干什么
Demon...
魔…
The eye of a mage is a powerful magical tool.
魔导士的眼珠 是强力的魔法道具
With this left eye,
只要有这颗左眼
you can undo the spell cast on the Demon King.
就能解开施展在魔王身上的法术
This is as much as I can do now...
这是目前我所能…
to show you my loyalty.
展现的最大忠诚
Is it all right for me to help him, Almond?
我可以帮助他吧 杏仁
Contain this place and head to the capital.
压制此处 直捣皇都
Bring that crystal along.
带上那颗水晶吧
I'M THE VILLAINESS, SO I'M TAMING THE FINAL BOSS!
《因为是反派大小姐》 《所以养了魔王》
THE VILLAINESS CAN ALSO BECOME THE PROTAGONIST WITH LOVE
(反派大小姐有爱也能成为主角)
-Stop. -Don't run.
-站住 -别跑
Arrest them!
抓住他们
Over here.
这里
Selena.
塞蕾娜
If you want to be saved, follow me.
想得救的话 就跟我走
I know where the Demon King is.
我也知道魔王在哪
Why are you helping us?
为什么要帮我们
If I help all of you, Lilia will...
帮助你们 莉莉安就…
All of you hate that woman, right?
你们讨厌那个女人吧
It's that simple.
仅此如此
Speaking of which,
话说回来
what does the Empress Dowager want to do by capturing mages as hostages?
皇太后抓魔导士为人质 到底想做什么
Don't you find it strange?
你不觉得奇怪吗
The Empress Dowager's youthful look is suspicious.
皇太后的外貌年轻得不合理
Could it be...
难道…是…
That's a waste of the mages' powers.
太浪费魔导士的能力了吧
Isaac! Keith!
艾札克 吉斯先生
Miss Aileen.
爱琳小姐
Why is the mage following you?
那个魔导士为何跟着你
He is an enemy, right?
他是敌人吧
It's fine. I've handled it.
没关系 我已经调教完了
The way you put it sounds...
我觉得这个说法有点…
What happened on your side?
你们那边 发生什么事了
Aren't the demons staying away from the capital?
不是要让魔物远离皇都吗
They are returning to the capital to save the Demon King.
它们返回皇都 打算去拯救魔王
Elephas, help me.
艾雷法斯 帮我
You should have some magic back, right?
你应该恢复一些魔力了吧
Wait. Miss Aileen!
等… 爱琳小姐
Aileen. Move out. The Demon King let out a cry.
爱琳 让开 魔王发出了悲鸣
Calm down, all of you.
你们冷静点
Master Claude would never summon you.
库洛德大人不可能呼唤你们吧
Are you saying we shouldn't save the Demon King?
你的意思是 别让我们去救魔王吗
Do you care more about the humans than the Demon King?
比起魔王 你更在乎人类吗
I will save Master Claude.
我会去救库洛德大人
Belzebuth. You will protect the demons.
佩鲁赛博特 你负责保护魔物们
Only until sunset.
到日落为止
Any longer, I will not wait.
再久 就不等了
I can take one person to the capital.
我能带一人去皇都
But the problem comes after that.
但之后才是问题
What do you mean?
什么意思
To get Master Claude back to normal,
要让库洛德大人恢复原状
this crystal has to be placed in the Empress Dowager's magic item.
必须将这颗水晶 放入皇太后的魔法道具里才行
But, I don't know where the magic item is.
可是 我不清楚魔法道具在何处…
Aileen. Can you hear me?
爱琳 听得到吗
Aileen!
爱琳
This voice is...
这个声音是…
James! I hear you!
赛姆斯 我听得到
Where are you now?
你现在在哪
I'm in the capital.
我在皇城的离宫
We found Master Claude
我们找到库洛德大人了
but he's heavily drugged with Demon Snuff and won't wake up.
但他似乎被浸在魔香中 昏迷不醒
-We've been surrounded. -Open the door.
-我们也被包围了 -开门
Is Rachel all right?
蕾切尔没事吧
She's fine. She's working harder than anyone.
没事 她比谁都还拼命
Anyway, the Demon King's cry was caused by the Demon Snuff.
总之 魔王的悲鸣是魔香引起的
The Demon King can blow off the Demon Snuff as long as His Highness regains his powers
只要魔王恢复魔力 就能一口气吹散魔香
but we don't know how to do that.
但我们不知该如何恢复魔王的魔力
Selena. Can you hear me?
塞蕾娜 听得到吗
Do you know about the Empress Dowager's magic item?
你知道皇太后的魔法道具吗
Magic item?
魔法道具
Don't you want to get Master Cedric?
你不是想得到塞多利克大人吗
You should have checked the palace, right?
应该调查过皇宫了吧
Even so, do you think I will tell you?
就算如此 你以为我会告诉你吗
I hate Lilia the most, and you're second to her.
我最讨厌莉莉安 第二讨厌的就是你
Selena.
塞蕾娜
Please. We need your strength.
拜托你 我们需要你的力量
It is most likely to be in the North Tower.
比较有可能的地方是北边的高塔
I heard that the important treasures are there.
听说重要的宝物都藏在那里
It makes sense. Even Holy Knights are not allowed there.
有道理 就算是圣骑士也不能靠近那里
Both of you are indeed a good match.
你们果然很登对
Auguste. Continue to be fooled by Selena.
奥古斯特继续被塞蕾娜骗吧
-What do you mean? -What are you saying?
-什么意思啊 -你在说什么啦
Aileen.
爱琳
We will protect Master Claude.
我们会保护库洛德大人
So, you have to be safe too.
所以 你也要平安无事
Otherwise, Master Claude would be sad.
不然 库洛德大人会难过的
Don't worry. I won't make him sad.
放心吧 我不会让他难过的
Over here.
这里
Are the hostages of the Levi tribe at the North Tower too?
被当成人质的雷比族人 也被关在北边的高塔吗
Yes.
是的
Sacred Sword? Could it be...
圣剑 难道…
LILIA RAINWORTH CV KANA HANAZAWA
(莉莉安 雷因华兹) (CV 花泽香菜)
REINCARNATION OF THE HOLY SWORD MAIDEN FROM A COMMONER TO BARON'S DAUGHTER
(圣剑少女的转世) (从平民摇身一变成为男爵千金)
AN INFLUENTIAL PERSON IN THE ACADEMY
(是学园里的风云人物)
EXCEPTIONALLY STRONG ABILITIES. BECOMING THE HOLY SWORD MAIDEN ACCORDING TO VARIOUS ROUTES
(体能高强 根据攻略路线不同) (成为拥有圣剑的女骑士)
HAS MEMORIES OF THE GAME JUST LIKE AILEEN. GOOD AT CONTROLLING CHARACTERS WITH WORDS
(与爱琳相同 拥有游戏记忆) (擅长使用言语操纵众多角色)
Elephas should be sentenced to death.
艾雷法斯应该被处死才对
I really like the pathetic storyline and even adjusted the affection levels.
我很喜欢那条凄惨的路线 还特地调整了好感度呢
Don't mind it. It's not something characters would understand.
别在意 这些话题角色听不懂
Isn't that right, Miss Aileen?
对吧 爱琳小姐
How's the content this time?
这次的内容如何
I've reflected and worked very hard on my previous attempt.
经过上次的经验 我彻底反省后 很努力重新来过哦
I think you're putting effort in the wrong direction.
我觉得你努力的方向错了
Is that so? It's very hard to obtain the Sacred Sword on Leister's route, you know?
会吗 可是走列斯塔路线 要取得圣剑很困难耶
What I have with me is the Sacred Sword from Cedric's route.
我手上的是塞多利克路线的圣剑
Lilia tamed a different character
莉莉安攻略了别的角色
and had the Sacred Sword resurrected.
重新让圣剑复活了
I'll distract her. You'll undo Master Claude's spell.
我来引开她 你趁机解开库洛德大人的法术
Let me ask you a question.
我问你一个问题
Why are you in my way?
为何要妨碍我
It's because I'm the only one who can defeat you.
因为 能跟你比个高下的人只有我
Don't lose too badly, Miss Aileen.
你可别输太惨哦 爱琳小姐
You're the protagonist.
因为 你是主角
If something happens to the Demon King, I'll not let you go.
如果魔王出了什么意外 我绝饶不了你们
Sure. Please swallow me whole starting from the head.
好啊 到时候请从头部开始一口吞
Honestly, I'm not a good person either.
其实我也不是什么好人
My wish is for a demon to swallow me.
被魔物吃掉是我的愿望
What are you saying?
什么跟什么啊
Actually, I envy you all.
其实 我很羡慕你们
Every time Master Claude is in pain,
库洛德大人感到痛苦时
I'm the only one who can't feel it.
每次都只有我 感觉不到
Belzebuth!
佩鲁赛博特先生
I finally caught up with you.
终于追上你们了
Did any demon get injured?
有没有魔物受伤
We brought medication.
我们带了药物过来
Don't get the old man worked up.
别让大叔太劳累
What are we supposed to do now?
现在该怎么办
Are we heading to the capital blindly after sunset?
太阳下山后 就像无头苍蝇般的突袭皇都吗
Or are we going together to save the Demon King?
还是跟着我们一起去救魔王
Why do you want to save the Demon King?
你们为何要救魔王
If you like Aileen,
如果是喜欢爱琳的话
the Demon King would be an obstacle.
魔王就是你们的情敌吧
Even if all of you worked together, you're no match for the Demon King.
你们几个加起来 也赢不了魔王
Bel. Read the room.
佩鲁 看一下气氛吧
Try to understand the complex heart of men, will you?
多了解一下复杂的少男心 好吗
Why are we saving the Demon King? It's simple.
为何要救魔王 原因很简单
Humans are stupid.
因为人类是笨蛋
With a heart, we can get along with anyone.
只要有心 能跟任何人相处融洽
Anyone?
任何人
That's right. With you all too.
没错 跟你们也行
It does seem like the way of humans.
很有人类的作风
Arrogant and self-righteous.
既傲慢 又自以为是
Curse you, protagonist bonuses.
该死的主角数值调整
The gamers' effort is always rewarded, that is why otome games are interesting.
玩家付出的努力必定有所回报 这就是乙女游戏的有趣之处
In that case, grow your etiquette stats too.
那你也多调整一下礼仪的数值
However, etiquette and strength stats are incompatible.
可是 礼仪和体力的数值不相容
However, villainesses usually have high basic specs, don't they?
不过 反派大小姐的基本数值 好像有点高
The only bad part is your personality, then?
那较差的数值是…性格吗
That's a wall I made out of the Sacred Sword.
那是用圣剑创造的结界墙
Don't disturb our joy, all right?
别打扰我的愉快时光
First things first, I'll relieve her of her sacred sword.
总之 先抢走你的圣剑
It hurts.
好痛
Seriously. It really hurts.
讨厌 真的好痛哦
Are you trying to snatch my Scared Sword?
你想抢走我的圣剑吗
I want you to return it to me.
是要你还给我
In the future, I'll be the one to destroy the demons and the Demon King.
之后不管是魔物还是魔王 都由我来毁灭
Enjoy this game with me.
多跟我一起享受这款游戏嘛
Won't you be bothered to know who the Holy Sword Maiden is?
你不会在意 圣剑少女到底是何方神圣吗
Holy Sword Maiden?
圣剑少女
I am the one who will become the Demon King's wife!
我可是…要成为魔王妻子的女人
What about Regalia of Saints, Demons and Maidens?
圣与魔与少女的雷加利亚又是什么
Whatever it is...
管他是什么…
Of course, it's the power of love.
当然是爱的力量啊
Are you serious?
你是认真的吗
You took the Demon King's power?
居然吸取魔王的力量
Are you trying to kill the Demon King?
你想杀死魔王吗
Master Claude won't die and leave me alone.
库洛德大人不会丢下我死去的
Moreover...
而且…
I just have to save Master Claude first.
只要我先救到库洛德大人就行了
No.
不行
The door is sealed with magic.
门被魔力封住了
What a pity!
真可惜
The magic is running out.
魔力用尽了
Master Claude is in danger.
库洛德大人…快不行了…
With all my magic...
把我所有的魔力…
Miss Aileen.
爱琳小姐
I'm the winner.
是我赢了
It's about time for me to make an entrance.
本大爷 差不多该登场了吧
No way...
不会…吧…
Almond!
杏仁
Save Master Claude!
快去救库洛德大人
Leave it to me!
交给我吧
What's going on?
怎么回事
I'm the best.
本大爷 超帅
Why? Could it be...
怎么会 难道…
We did it...
成功了…
The magic must have been lifted.
如此一来 法术应该解开了
This is the end!
到此为止
Aileen Lauren Dautriche.
爱琳 罗伦 多德勒
You should be executed for disobeying the order.
你因违反勒令 应遭处刑
What a pity. Aileen will end up being punished heavily.
真可怜 爱琳小姐的下场 居然是遭到处以极刑
Who are you pointing your swords at?
你们的剑尖正指向谁
Master Claude...
库洛德…大人…
Demon King!
魔王大人 魔王大人
Stand down.
全部退下
But the order...
可是…勒令…
The order is cancelled.
勒令取消
The King is unwell. He needs to take some rest.
国王陛下身体不适 需好好静养
Hence, as the Imperial Prince, I will take over his duties.
所以由我王太子暂代职务
Is that right, Cedric?
对吧 塞多利克
As you said, Brother.
既然王兄这么说 那就这么办吧
What is happening?
这是怎么回事
Leister.
列斯塔
I investigated your purchase of the Demon Snuff at the auction.
我查到你从地下拍卖会上 得到了魔香
Marcus used it very well.
马库斯也用得很顺手
What...
什…
What's going on?
什么 怎么回事
Lilia. You are a horrible woman.
莉莉安 你真是可怕的女人
Everyone is working for you
每个人都为你做事
but you pretend as if you know nothing.
但你却装作不知情的模样
Brother.
王兄
The fault is mine for not controlling my people.
此次事件 是因为我管教下人不当
My fiancee is also guilty.
我的未婚妻也同罪
Please punish us.
请处分
Cedric.
塞多利克
Lilia. I will not listen to you or be controlled by you anymore.
莉莉安 我不会再听你的 不再被你所操纵
Even so, my love for you will never change.
即便如此 我对你的爱永远不变
Aileen.
爱琳
You must be scared.
你很害怕吧
It's all right now.
已经没事了
Aileen. Come here.
爱琳 过来
After the King and Queen receive treatment,
在国王与皇太后前去疗养后
Master Claude announced
库洛德大人公开宣布
"I'm getting married to Aileen."
"我将与爱琳结婚"
The Levi tribe has also been pardoned by Master Claude.
雷比一族 也由库洛德大人下令 获得解放
Their safety is now guaranteed.
关于他们的遭遇 也正式受到保障
Almond is still as strong as he is.
杏仁还是如往常一般很有精神
He's practising the dance for the wedding ceremony.
现在正在练习 在结婚典礼上表演的舞蹈
It seems that Elephas' magic arrow had him in a state of thanatosis.
艾雷法斯射出的魔法箭 似乎只让它呈现假死状态
The mage who insisted on not killing demons is best suited as the final boss.
魔导士坚持不杀魔物 非常适合担任最后大魔王
Master Cedric and Lilia live happily ever after in their prison.
塞多利克大人与莉莉安小姐 甜甜蜜蜜地走向入狱悲怆结局
A bright future
原本前途无光的未来
that's supposed to head towards a dark end
直奔毁灭的路线
is now as bright as ever.
如今却如此闪耀无比
It doesn't matter what the future holds.
以后 无论遇到什么困难都无所谓
Even if a bad ending was right here,
即便BE就在眼前
it cannot stop the strong love between two people.
也抵挡不了两人坚定的爱